calculateforfree.com 2012-11-25

# online Calculator

---|---  
  
##  Privacy Policy 

Thank you for visiting Calculateforfree.com.. Your privacy is very important to us. Simply stated, our policy is to collect no personal information about you when you visit the Calculateforfree Web site, unless you affirmatively choose to make such information available to us. 

When you visit the Calculateforfree.com web site, the Web server automatically recognizes only the Internet domain and IP address from which you accessed the site. This information does not result in the identification of your personal e-mail address or other personal information.

In addition, information is only gathered regarding the volume and timing of access to the site by collecting information on the date, time and pages you visited while at the site. This is done so that the content of the site can be improved, and your personal information is not identified.

We do not collect information or profile our visitors in any way. This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, calculateforfree.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

##  Cookies

Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. You can visit the  [ Network Advertising Initiative ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/)   if you want to find out more information about this practice, and to learn about your options, including your options with regard to the following companies that may serve advertising on this site:  
[[ MSN ] ](http://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/fullnotice.mspx#display)   [[ Value click media ] ](http://valueclickmedia.com/privacy.shtml)   [[ Casale Media.com ] ](http://casalemedia.com/privacy.html)   [[ Advertising.com ] ](http://advertising.aol.com/privacy)   [[ NetSeer ] ](http://netseer.com/privacypolicy.html)   [[ Chitika ] ](http://chitika.com/privacy)   [[ Adsense ] ](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html)

### Online Calculator, sure beats the old slide ruler
